Guide to the Brian Lassiter Hip Hop Collection, circa 1980-2013.
Lassiter, Brian Hip Hop Collection
- Series V. Lassiter Hip-Hop and Music Related Magazines and Periodicals Collection
  - Magazines and other periodicals, 1979-2015
    - Titles I-O
      - Mix, 1992-11-1995-09 (Box 20)
        Vol. 16 No. 11; Vol. 17 No. 12; Vol. 18 No. 7, 8; Vol. 19 No. 7, 9
      - Mix Bookshelf, 1995 (Box 50)
      - Mixplus East, 1994 (Box 20)
      - MM Modeling, 2004-08 (Box 64)
      - Modern Drummer, Winter/Spring 1995 (Box 50)
        Vol. 9 No. 4, Vol. 10 No. 1
      - Modern Recording and Music, 1980-09 (Box 50)
        Vol. 5 No. 12
      - Molotov Cocktail, Undated (Box 50)
        "New York Special"
      - Money Maker, 1991-04-1991-05 (Box 50)
        Vol. 12 No. 3
      - Mundo Hispanico, 2015-06-11-2015-06-17 (Box 59)
        Spanish Language news paper. Vol. 36 no. 1, 247
      - Murder Dog, 1997-1999 (Box 20)
        no # (1997-1998), Vol. 5 No. 5, Vol. 6 No. 3
      - Murder Dog, 2000-2002 (Box 21)
        Vol. 7 No. 2, 5, 6; Vol. 8 No. 1 (St. Lunatics Cover only), 2, 3, 4 (St. Lunatics Cover); Vol. 9 No. 1 (Dungeon Family Cover)
      - Murder Dog, 2002-2007 (Box 22)
        Vol. 9 No. 2 (Grind Family Cover), 3 (Xzibit Cover), 4 (Jackson, MS); Vol. 10 No. 1 (50 Cent Cover), 2 (David Banner Cover), 4 (Westside Connection Cover); Vol. 11 No. 1 (Messy Marv Cover), 3 (Federation Cover), 4 (T.I. Cover); Vol. 12 No. 2 (Z-Ro Cover), 3 (Paul Wall Cover), 4 (Keak Da Sneak Cover); Vol. 13 No. 2 (Bullys Wit Fullys Cover); Vol. 14 No. 1 (Young Jeezy Cover), 2 (Chamillionaire Cover)
      - Murder Dog, 2008-2009 (Box 23)
        Vol. 15 No. 1 (Rick Ross Cover), 2 (Keak da Sneak Cover), 3 (The Game Cover); Vol. 16 No. 1, 2 (Bye Bye Cover)
      - Music and Sound Output, 1986-09-1988-01 (Box 50)
        Vol. 6 No. 10, Vol. 7 No. 9, Vol. 8 No. 2
      - Music Business International, 1995-08 (Box 59)
        Vol. V no. IV
      - Music Business Wire, 2002 (Box 50)
        Q2 Vol. 2
      - Music Connection, 1985-02-1985-11 (Box 50)
        Vol. 9 No. 4, Vol. 9 No. 23
      - Music Technology Magazine, The, 1986-09-1988-09 (Box 50)
        Vol. 1 No. 2, Vol. 1 No. 3, Vol. 3 No. 2
      - Music Week, 1995-09-02 (Box 59)
      - Musician, 1984-02-1997-09 (Box 51)
        No. 64, No. 77, No. 223, No. 227
      - Musician: Player and Listener, 1980-01-1982-03 (Box 51)
        No. 22, No. 24, No. 41
      - My People, 1998-2003 (Box 64)
        Vol. 1 Issue 2-3; Volume 2 Issue 2; Volume 5 Issue 2
      - National Small Business Journal, 1994 (Box 51)
        Vol. 1 No. 2
      - National Small Business Journal, 1995-03-1995-04 (Box 60)
        Vol. 2, No. 2
      - Native Peoples, 1997 (Box 51)
        "Special 10th Anniversary Issue"
      - Neo, 2003-2004 (Box 64)
        Vol. 1 Issue 6; Vol. 2 Issue 11
      - New Funk Times, The, 1980-12 (Box 60)
        Vol. 1, No. 2
      - New Power, The, 2004 (Box 60)
        Vol. 2, No. 3
      - New Power, The, 2007 (Box 64)
        Vol. 5 No. 1; Vol. 8 No. 1; Vol. 9 No. 1
      - New Visions, 1995 (Box 51)
      - New York Magazine, 1980-11-24 (Box 51)
        Vol. 13 No. 46
      - Newsweek, Fall 1997 (Box 51)
        November 28, 1988; May 11, 1992; November 16, 1992; March 17, 1997; October 9, 2000
      - Notorious, 1999 (Box 51)
      - Now Entertainment, Summer 1999 (Box 64)
        Vol. 1 No. 1; Vol. 9 No. 9
      - N-Touch News, 1997-04-24 (Box 60)
        Vol. 1, No. 18
      - NY Talk, 1986-11 (Box 60)
        Vol. 3 No. 30
      - ODS: On Da Streets, 2006 (Box 51)
        Vol. 2 Issue 1, 8 Ball and MJG issue
      - Off Beat, 1990-05-1993-05 (Box 52)
        Vol. 3 No. 5, Vol. 6 No. 5
      - On Common Ground, 2002-08 (Box 24)
        Vol. 8 Issue 5
      - On Common Ground, 2000-03-2015-03-14 (Box 52)
        Vol. 5, Issue 12; Vol. 7, Issue 5; Vol. 13 No. 15; Vol. 15, no. 20; Vol. 20, No. 50
      - On Point, 1996-08 (Box 24)
      - On the Beat: The Dance Music Letter, Undated (Box 52)
      - On the Go, 1997 (Box 24)
        Issue 17
      - One Nut, 1994-03-1998-06 (Box 24)
        Issue 15 (March 1994)
      - One World, 1998 (Box 52)
      - Onyx, 1999 (Box 24)
        Issue 3; Summer Issue; Vol. 2 No. 8; Vol. 3 No. 9
      - Option, Fall 1998 (Box 24)
        No. 24, 38, 57, 58, 80
      - Our Heritage, 1995 (Box 52)
        Vol. 1 No. 3
      - Owners Illustrated, 2005 (Box 52)
        Premier Issue; Issue V
        2 copies of issue V - with different covers
      - Oz, Winter 1995 (Box 52)
        Volume 3 Issue 5; Volume 4 Issue 3, 4
      - Ozone Magazine, 2004-04-2005-09; CD-2484-2488 (Box 24)
        Issue 22, 30-33, 35-38 (CDs in 33, 35-38)
      - Ozone Magazine, 2005-11-2007-05; CD-2489-2490 (Box 25)
        Issue 39-41, 43, 45-51, 53-56 (CDs in 39, 43)
      - Ozone (mini), 2005-2006 (Box 64)
        14 issues
      - Jermaine Dupri - Sampler, 2005; CD-2498 (Box 64)
        In Ozone mini Memorial Day edition 2005
      - Rick Ross and DJ Khaled - Ozone Sampler, 2006; CD-2496 (Box 64)
        In Ozone mini Memorial Day edition 2006
    - Titles P-Z
      - Penthouse, 1993-04 (Box 52)
      - People Weekly, 1988-09-26 (Box 52)
        Vol. 30 No. 13
      - People You Need to Know, 2008 (Box 52)
      - People's Underground Beat (PUB), 2000 (Box 60)
      - Philadelphia Inquirer Magazine, The, 1997-06-03 (Box 60)
        Section D
      - Planet Atlanta, 1994-03 (Box 60)
        Vol. 1, no. 3
      - Planet Black, Fall 2000 (Box 60)
        Vol. 1, No. 46
      - Platinum, 2000-09-2000-10 (Box 52)
      - Platinum Entrepreneur, 2006 (Box 53)
        "Premier Issue"
      - Plugged, 2000-07 (Box 65)
      - PowerPlay Magazine, 2000 (Box 53)
      - Pro Sound News, 1993-1995-08 (Box 60)
        Vol. 15 - Vol. 16, Replication News
      - Pro Sound News: Special 10th Anniversary Supplement, 1988- (Box 53)
      - Profiles, 1996-10-1997-02 (Box 65)
      - Progress Report, The, 2006 (Box 53)
      - Props Magazine, 1996-1997 (Box 25)
        Vol. 4 No. 14, 16; Vol. 5 No. 17
      - Pulse!, 1991-08-1993-11 (Box 25)
        No. 96, 120
      - Pulse!, 1993-12-2001-06 (Box 26)
        No. 121, 123-124, 126, 128-130, 133, 150, 155, 180, 184, 204
      - R&B Music Guide/Rap Guide Magazine, 1997-1999 (Box 26)
        Vol. 7 Issue 1, 2, 5; Vol. 8 Issue 3-4; Vol. 9 Issue 1
      - R&B Report, The, 1989-02-1989-03 (Box 53)
        Vol. 2 No. 23
      - Rap Pages, 1996-2000-07 (Box 27)
        Vol. 5 No. 3, 9; Vol. 6 No. 2 (1996-1997)
      - Rap Sheet, 1999-05-2000-10 (Box 27)
        1993-1994; Vol. 8 No. 5, 10; Vol. 9 No. 8
      - RAW: Real African World, 1994 (Box 60)
      - Real Talk, 2007 (Box 53)
      - Reality, 2000-12 (Box 65)
      - Record, 1984-03 (Box 53)
      - Recording Engineer/Producer, 1985-1992 (Box 53)
        Vol. 16 No. 6, Vol. 18 No. 1,3, Vol. 21 No. 5, Vol. 21 No. 8, 11, Vol. 22 No. 2, 10, Vol. 23 No. 6, 8
        Changed name from Recording Engineer/Producer to REP: Recording/Engineering/Production
      - Reggae Bloodlines, 1995-04-14 (Box 53)
        Vol. 1 No. 1
      - Reggae Nation, 1994-09-1994-10 (Box 53)
      - Reggae Nucleus Magazine, 1997-07-1997-08 (Box 53)
        Vol. 4 No. 4
      - Reggae Times, 1996 (Box 53)
      - Remix, 2001-03-2001-10 (Box 27)
        Vol. 3 No. 3, 8-10
      - Rhythm and Bass, 1998-05 (Box 65)
      - Rhythm Review, The, 1998-08 (Box 65)
        Issue 15
      - Rides, April/May 2005, Winter 2005 (Box 54)
      - Right On!, 1988-10 (Box 54)
      - Ring, The, 1982-11 (Box 54)
        Vol. 61 No. 9
      - RMM: Rhythm Music Magazine, 1994-03 (Box 54)
        Vol. 3 No. 3
      - Rocharder Magazine, 2009 (Box 28)
        3 versions of Vol. 1 Issue 1. "Premier Edition"
      - Rolling Out Atlanta, 1999-01-07-2013-06-13 (Box 60)
        Vol. 1 no. 3, no. 6, no. 14; Vol. 4 No. 24; Vol. 6 No. 33, 44; Vol. 10 No. 28; Vol. 14 no. 23
      - Rolling Stone, 1984-05-10-1992-08-20 (Box 60)
        Issue No. 421, 545, 549, 637
      - Roots Publication, 1997-1999 (Box 28)
        Vol. 2 Issue 17; Vol. 4 Issue 27; Vol. 5 Issue 31-32
      - RPM: Revolutions per Minute, 1993-01-1993-12 (Box 28)
        Vol. 1 Issue 6 (Nov/Dec 1993)
      - Savoy, 2001-10 (Box 54)
        Vol. 1 Issue 8
      - Score Atlanta, 2006-01-04-2006-01-10 (Box 54)
      - Score Atlanta, 2006-01-04-2006-01-10 (Box 61)
        Vol. 2, No. 1
      - Seaspot, 2003 (Box 54)
      - Showcase Magazine, 1998-2000 (Box 28)
        Issue 8, Issue 14
      - Sister 2 Sister, 2001-10-2005-10 (Box 54)
        Vol. 13 No. 10, Vol. 17 No. 10
      - Sizurp, Undated (Box 54)
      - Sizurp The DVD, Undated; DVD-1494 (Box 54)
        Vol. 3
      - SMPTE Journal (Society of Motion Picture and Television Engineers), 1978-12-1979-10 (Box 54)
        Vol. 87 No. 12 - Vol. 88 No. 2, Vol. 88 No. 5, Vol. 88 No. 10
      - Soul Survivor, 1984 (Box 54)
      - Soul Underground, 1990-04 (Box 54)
        Issue 30
      - Sound Choice, 1985 (Box 55)
      - Source, The, Fall 1985 (Box 28)
        No. 19, 37, 38, 43, 45, 46, 48, 50-53
      - Source, The, 1994-09-1997-11 (Box 29)
        No. 60, 67, 73, 76, 84, 86, 88, 90, 93-96, 98
      - Source, The, 1997-08-1999-04 (Box 30)
        No. 100-104, 109,111-113, 115
      - Source, The, 1999-05-2000-08 (Box 31)
        No. 116-118, 123-124, 126, 128-129, 131
      - Source, The, 2000-09-2001-08 (Box 32)
        No. 132-133, 135, 139, 141-143
      - Source, The, 2002-06-2004-10 (Box 33)
        No. 153, 156, 165, 168, 181
      - South Coast Music Guide (SCMG), 1997-06-1997-11 (Box 65)
        Vol. 1 No. 3, 6
      - South: The Third World Magazine, 1983-12 (Box 55)
        No. 38
      - Southeast Minority Owned Retailers Coalition, 1998-1999 (Box 65)
        Vol. 1 Issue 5; Vol. 2; Vol. 2 Issue 1; Vol. 2 Issue 3-5; Vol. 3 Issue 1; Vol. 4
      - Southeast Performer, 1999-2001 (Box 33)
        Vol. 1 Issue 6; Vol. 2 Issue 2, 11-12; Vol. 11 Issue 6-10
      - Southeast Performer, 2002 (Box 34)
        Vol. 12 Issue 2, 11
      - Spectrum, 1995-1999-01 (Box 61)
        Catalogue, 3 Issues
      - Spin, 1987-01-1994-05 (Box 61)
        Vol. 2, No. 10; Vol. 4, No. 1; Vol. 4, No. 7; Vol. 6, No. 11; Vol. 9, No. 7; Vol. 10, No. 2
      - Sports Illustrated, 1983-06-27 (Box 55)
        Vol. 58 No. 26
      - Still Here, 1983-02-1984-02 (Box 55)
        Vol. 13 No. 7, Vol. 14 No. 7
      - Straight from the Street, 1994-02 (Box 61)
        Vol. 3, No. 9
      - Street and Smith's Sports Business Journal, 1999-04-26-1999-05-02 (Box 61)
        Vol. 2 Issue 1
      - Street Flava, 1994-12-1997 (Box 34)
        Vol. 2, Vol. 5, no Vol. #
        December 1994, 1996, Spring 1997
      - Street Magazine, 2008 (Box 55)
      - Street Report, 2009-05-2010-11 (Box 55)
      - Street Sound, 1991-03-13-1991-05-18 (Box 61)
        No. 46, 48
      - Street Talk Newspaper, 2006-05-2008-02 (Box 61)
        5 Issues: Issue 6-7, 15
      - Streetbuzz, The, 2005-12 (Box 55)
      - Streetmasters, 2003-09-2007 (Box 34)
        "Premiere Special Collector's Issue", Vol. 1 Issue 2-7, 13-14, 16-17, 19, 21, 23
      - Streets Mos', 2009 (Box 55)
        Issue 10
      - Stress, 1997-1998; SR-6712 (Box 34)
        Issue 6, 10, 12, 13
        Issue 12 has soundsheet
      - Stress, 1998-1999; CD-2491 (Box 35)
        Issue 15-19
      - Studio Sound and Broadcast Engineering, 1987-09 (Box 55)
        Vol. 29 No. 9
      - Style Magazine, 1998-06-24-1998-07-01 (Box 61)
        Vol. 8, No. 21
      - Success, 2000-06 (Box 55)
      - Sunday Paper, The, 2005-07-10-2005-07-16 (Box 61)
      - Supreme, 2000-07-2001-02 (Box 35)
        No. 2, 5, 6
      - Sweater, 1997 (Box 55)
        No. 1
      - Swing Loe: Atlanta's Local Black Music Guide, 1994 (Box 55)
      - Tafrija (large format), Spring 1994 (Box 62)
        Vol. 3 - Vol. 5,
      - Tafrija (regular format), 1996-1997 (Box 63)
        Vol. 7 - Vol. 8
      - Taking It By Force, 1999 (Box 55)
      - Talking Drums, 1989-03-1989-04 (Box 35)
        Volume 1 Issue 1-2
      - Teen Time Today, 1999-10 (Box 55)
        Vol. 3 Issue 14
      - Teenpreneur, 2003-03 (Box 55)
      - Tha Hole, 2003-11-2004-01 (Box 55)
        No. 5
      - Ticket, The, 1994-08 (Box 55)
      - TIME, 1995-10-30-1999-02-08 (Box 55)
        Vol. 146 No. 18, Vol. 153 No. 5
      - Touch Magazine, 1995-08 (Box 55)
        Issue 50
      - Transition: An International Review, 1992 (Box 55)
        Issue 57
      - Unda$tream (Undastream), The, 2005 (Box 47)
        Issue 4
      - Underground Railroad, The, 2007-12-2008-02 (Box 47)
      - Underground Soundz, 1997 (Box 47)
      - Uptown, 1996-04-1996-05 (Box 62)
      - URB, 1999-07 (Box 47)
        Vol. 9 No. 66
      - Urb Magazine, 1994-04 (Box 62)
        No. 35
      - Urban, 1996-1999 (Box 47)
        No. 6; Vol. 3 No. 4; Vol. 4 No. 1
      - Urban America, 2001-09 (Box 62)
        Vol. 1, 2nd Edition
      - Urban Beat, 1995-02-1998-07 (Box 62)
        Vol. 1, Issue 2; Vol. 1 Issue 4; Vol. 4, Issue 7
      - Urban Grind, 1994-04 (Box 47)
        Vol. 2 Issue 4
      - Urban Ink, 2008 (Box 47)
        Vol. 11 No. 88
      - Urban Network, The, 1994-11-18-1994-11-25 (Box 62)
        Issue 343, 344
      - Urbanews, 2005-11-2007-08 (Box 65)
      - USA Today, 1989-08-22 (Box 62)
      - Vibe, 1993-11-1996-08 (Box 35)
        Vol. 1 No. 3; Vol. 2 No. 1-3; Vol. 3 No. 7; Vol. 4 No. 5-6
      - Vibe, 1996-09-2002-01 (Box 36)
        Vol. 4 No. 7, 9; Vol. 6 No. 3, 6-7; Vol. 7 No. 8; September 2000; August 2001; January 2002
      - Village Voice, The, 1988-10-1987-09-01 (Box 62)
        Vol. 1, No. 1; Vol. 32, No. 35
      - Warner Communications Inc. 1979 Annual Report, 1979 (Box 47)
      - Wavelength, 1986-10 (Box 62)
        No. 72
      - Waxpoetics, 2010-05-2010-06 (Box 63)
        Vol. 41
      - World Famous, Undated (Box 47)
        Vol. 1 Issue 5, Vol. 1 Issue 7
      - Xplosive, 2003 (Box 47)
        Vol. 6; Vol. 6 Issue 1; Vol. 10
      - XXL, 1997-2002-05 (Box 37)
        Issue 1, 5-7; Vol. 3 No. 2-3; Vol. 4 No. 1, 6; Vol. 5, No. 6, 11-12; Vol. 6 No. 3-4
      - XXL, 2002-06-2003-08 (Box 38)
        No. 37-46, 47-50
      - XXL, 2003-09-2004-11 (Box 39)
        No. 51-52, 54-56, 58, 60-64
      - XXL, 2004-12-2005-12 (Box 40)
        No. 65-66, 68-76
      - XXL, 2006-01-2008-02 (Box 41)
        "Shade45"; No. 78, 80-82, 84-89, 94, 97, 99
      - XXL, 2008-03-2008-07 (Box 42)
        No. 100, 102-104
      - Your Money, 1993-10-1993-11 (Box 47)
        Vol. 14 No. 6
      - YSB, 1991-1994-07 (Box 47)
        "Premier Issue", Vol. 3 No. 2, Vol. 3 No. 9